People in the UK work longer hours than anyone else in the European Union but are far from the most productive.
英国人的工作时长比欧盟其他任何国家的人都要长，但工作效率却远非最高。
According to the Trades Union Congress, a UK body that brings together 49 member unions to improve their working conditions, employees in Denmark are 24% more productive per hour but work four hours fewer per week.
英国工会大会是一个由49个成员工会组成的机构，致力于改善劳动者的工作条件。该机构的数据显示，丹麦员工的每小时工作效率与英国员工相比高出24%，但每周工作时长却少4个小时。
'Britain's long-hours culture… is robbing workers of a decent home life and time with their loved ones.
英国工会大会秘书长弗朗西斯·奥格雷迪表示：“英国的超长工作时长文化……
Overwork, stress and exhaustion have become the new normal,' says TUC General Secretary Frances O'Grady.
正在剥夺劳动者应有的正常家庭生活和陪伴亲人的时间。
They want businesses to cut the standard working week from five days to four.
过度工作、压力缠身和身心疲惫已经成了新常态。”该机构希望企业将标准工作周从五天缩短至四天。
But would a four-day week work?
但四天工作制真的可行吗？
It does for Rich Leigh, founder of a Gloucester-based PR business.
对于格洛斯特一家公关公司的创始人里奇·利来说，四天工作制是可行的。
Staff there work Monday to Thursday, 9am – 5:30pm, but still get paid the same as before.
他公司的员工每周一到周四工作，朝九晚五点半，但薪资待遇和以前一样。
In an interview with the BBC, Leigh claims it makes the staff happier, which leads to better, more productive work.
利在接受英国广播公司采访时称，这种工作制让员工更开心，进而能更出色、更高效地完成工作。
After a year, earnings and profits are up and sick days have halved.
实行一年后，公司的营收和利润有所增长，员工病假天数也减少了一半。
The 4 Day Week Campaign also believes a shorter week would benefit everyone.
“四天工作制运动”组织也认为，缩短工作周会让所有人受益。
They claim that it would, among other things, more evenly distribute work between the overworked and the underemployed.
该组织称，除了其他好处外，这种制度还能更公平地在超负荷工作者和未充分就业者之间分配工作任务。
They estimate that around 30 UK businesses operate a 'four day, same pay' system.
他们估计，英国约有30家企业正在实行“四天工作、薪资不变”的制度。
However, not everyone is convinced.
不过，并非所有人都信任这种制度。
One of the UK's leading charities, the Wellcome Trust, conducted an organisation-wide consultation into whether a four-day week would fit. They decided against it.
英国顶尖慈善机构之一的惠康基金会在全组织范围内开展了一项调研，探讨四天工作制是否适用，最终决定不采用该制度。
'Many employees worried about their five-day workloads being compressed into just four days and some raised concerns that the time and energy used to implement a four-day week would distract the charity from its core work,' says Ed Whiting, director of policy at the Trust.
基金会政策主管埃德·怀廷表示：“许多员工担心原本五天的工作量会被压缩到四天内完成，还有一些人担忧，推行四天工作制所耗费的时间和精力会让基金会偏离核心工作。”
So does a four-day working week work or not?
那么，四天工作制到底可行吗？
Clearly it suits some… but not everyone.
显然，它适用于部分企业……但并非所有企业。
"We've got a lot to do before it can work for different sectors," says Emelia Quist from the Federation of Small Businesses in a BBC interview.
英国小企业联合会的埃米莉亚·奎斯特在接受英国广播公司采访时表示：“要让这种制度在不同行业落地，我们还有很多工作要做。”
'Social care needs people present 24/7.
她补充道：“社会关怀行业需要有人全天候在岗。
How can we ensure those industries can work a four-day week?' she adds.
我们该如何确保这类行业也能实行四天工作制呢？”
Until we can answer questions like these, there's clearly more work to be done.
在我们能够解答诸如此类的问题之前，显然还有很长的路要走。